{
    "subject": "resource/Phil_Urso",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1925-10-02",
    "human_readable": "Phil Urso was born on October 2, 1925.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8520800471305847,
            "question": "When was Phil Urso born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8195105195045471,
            "question": "If today was October 2nd, would it be Phil Urso's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8115518093109131,
            "question": "October 2nd of what year marks Phil Urso's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.714106023311615,
            "question": "On which date did Phil Urso celebrate his birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6916806697845459,
            "question": "What is Phil Urso's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5877256393432617,
            "question": "What month and day was Phil Urso born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.54979008436203,
            "question": "What is the day of the week that Phil Urso was born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5396543741226196,
            "question": "Is Phil Urso's birthday in the fall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4363288879394531,
            "question": "In what year did Phil Urso come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3709895610809326,
            "question": "What is Phil Urso's birthdate in the format MM DD YYYY?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phil Urso was born on October 2, 1925.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1913_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Phil Urso come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1913_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Phil Urso's birthday in the fall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1913_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the day of the week that Phil Urso was born on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1913_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1913_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that Phil Urso was indeed born on October 2, 1925, as mentioned in various texts."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that Phil Urso was born on October 2, 1925."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}